《黑镜》
《金属头》
给我剥一个
Open one of those for us.
只有你受得了这些糖
You know you're the only one who can stand these things?
只剩这玩意了
They're the only things left.
那些猪全没了
The pigs have all gone.
以前那里全是猪
Used to be full of pigs, that.
是啊  还有猪粪
Yeah, that and pig shit.
狗把它们都消灭了
Dogs took care of them.
我觉得我受不了做猪
Don't think I could hack being a pig.
我也觉得你不行
I don't think you could either.
做猪有什么不好的
What's so bad about being a pig?
没有尊严
It's undignified.
Undignified?
鼻子和屁眼在一个高度
Walking about with your nose the same height as your asshole.
- 吻  - 什么
- Snout. - What's that?
猪鼻子叫吻  不叫鼻子
Pigs have snouts, not noses.
所以应该是你的吻和屁眼一个高度
So it would be your snout the same height as your asshole.
鼻  吻
Nose, snout.
整天还是得
You're still trotting about
盯着别人的屁眼跑来跑去
gazing up everybody else's assholes all day long.
这算什么社会
What kind of society is that?
平等的社会
An equal one?
你觉得呢
So what do you reckon?
行不行
Yes or no?
我可以试试  你们不会去太久吧
I can give it a go. You're not gonna be long?
最多五分钟
Five minutes, max.
该死的
Fucking hell.
这真是太疯狂了
This is mental, this is.
反正他也要死了
I mean, he's dying anyway.
的确是嘛
Well, he is.
反正这样也救不了他
I mean, it's not like it's gonna save him.
他只剩几天了吧
He's got, what, days?
如果这里面的东西能让他最后几天舒坦些
Well, if it's what's in there makes those days easier...
我就满足了
that'll do for me.
我向我妹妹保证过我们会帮他
I promised my sister we'd help him.
我们都向她保证了
We all promised her.
再说里面还会有其他东西  电池
Plus there'll be other stuff in there. Batteries.
- 各种东西  - 好吧  好吧
- All sorts. - OK. OK.
钥匙别拔
Leave the keys in the ignition.
还用得着你说吗
I'm ahead of you there.
如果你听到什么动静  不要久留
If you hear anything, yeah, don't fuck about, yeah?
赶紧跑
Just tear straight off.
- 五分钟  - 一分不多
- Five minutes? - No more.
好吗
All right?
你确定会在里面吗
You sure it's gonna be in there?
我当然不确定了
Course I'm not sure.
管他呢
Fuck it.
(启动密码错误)
该死
Fuck.
95dy42
95-dy42.
(启动密码错误)
95dy42
95-dy42.
95dy...
95-dy...
95dy42
95-dy42.
快
Quick.
该死
Fuck.
快走  快走
Go. Go.
Go! Go!
托尼
Tony!
克拉克  快走
Clarke! Go!
该死
Oh, fuck.
拜托
Come on.
对了
Yes.
不
No!
该死
Fucking hell.
不  不要啊
No, please!
拜托  不  不  不要啊
Please, no! Fuck, no! No, please!
不要
Please!
该死
Fuck!
滚
Fucker!
该死
Fuck!
滚  滚开  滚开
Fuck. Fuck you, you... Fuck!
好吧
Ok.
该死
Shit.
好吧
Ok.
有人吗
Anyone?
收得到吗
Come in?
如果你听得到  我是贝拉
If you can hear me, it's Bella.
有人吗
Hello?
接啊  拜托  接啊
Pick up. Please, fucking pick up.
该死
Fuck.
喂  你是谁
Hello? Who is that?
我听不到你说话  你声音不清楚
I can't hear you. You're not clear.
如果你听得到我说话  吹口哨
Listen, if you can hear me, just whistle.
不要说话
Don't say anything.
好  好
Ok, ok.
我不能说太久
I can't talk for long.
我们在仓库发现一只狗
We found a dog at the warehouse.
我们没看到
We didn't see it.
我们不知道那只狗在那里多久了
We don't know how long it had been in there.
它干掉了托尼和克拉克
It got Tony and Clarke.
他们死了  对不起
So they're gone. I'm... I'm sorry.
你能再转告艾丽我很抱歉吗
And can you tell Ali that I'm sorry too?
她说我们根本不该去  她说得没错
She said that we were mad to bother and she was right.
我们...只是想帮她安抚杰克
We... We just wanted to help her with Jack.
我不知道
I don't know...
给他拿点有帮助的东西
Get him something that might help.
我知道他很痛苦
I know he's in pain.
我暂时甩掉那只狗了
I've lost the dog for now,
但我猜它还在运行
but my guess is it's still operational.
我想它应该能锁定这个信号
And I'm figuring it can lock onto this signal,
所以我要中止通讯了
so I'm gonna have to go dark.
我腿上中了它的追踪器
It's, um... It stuck me with a tracker,
但我想办法取出来了
but I managed to get it out.
我要找个能过夜的地方躲起来  我...
I'm gonna have to find somewhere overnight to hide out, I...
找点药之类的
Get some medical stuff or something.
如果我没能回去
If I don't make it back...
能帮我给格雷姆带个话吗
will you pass a message to Graham?
就告诉他我爱他
Just I love him.
能帮我转达吗
Please would you pass that on?
我得关闭对讲机了
I'm gonna have to switch off now.
我会努力回去的
I'll try and make it back.
再见
Bye, now.
该死
Fuck.
Fuck!
该死
加把劲
Come on.
别动
Stay still.
该死  该死  该死
Shit, shit, shit.
你上不来
You can't do it.
你前爪废了  你爬不上来
Your arm's fucked, so you can't climb the tree.
好好看看吧  伙计
Yeah, take a good look, mate.
你要等上很久了
You'll be waiting a long time.
很久很久
A very long time.
上帝啊
God.
欢迎醒来
Welcome back.
1,000...
999,
998,
997,
996...
九  八  七
...nine, eight, seven,
六  五  四
six, five, four,
三  二  一
three, two, one.
1,000...
999...
四
four...
三
three...
二
two...
一
one.
1,000...
999...
998...
三  二  一
...three, two, one.
993  992
993, 992...
太好了
Yes.
四  三
...four, three,
二  一
two, one.
该死
Oh, fuck.
Ah, fuck!
拜托
Ah, come on.
Oh, come on.
该死
Oh, shit.
拜托  拜托  拜托
Come on. Come on, come on.
车钥匙  车钥匙  车钥匙
Car keys, car keys, car keys. Car keys.
车钥匙
Car keys.
该死
Oh, fuck.
钥匙  钥匙  拜托
Keys, keys, keys. Come on.
该死
Oh, fuck.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
该死
Oh, fuck.
好了  好了  好了
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
该死  该死  该死
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
拜托  拜托
Come on. Come on.
拜托
Come on.
该死
Fuck.
有人在吗
Is there anyone there?
能听到我说话吗
Maybe you can hear me?
有人能听到我说话吗
Maybe someone can hear me.
如果有人在的话
If there is anyone there...
我只是要说我不会回去了
This is just to say that I'm not coming back.
告诉艾丽我很抱歉
Say I'm sorry to Ali and
让她替我给杰克一个吻
that she should give Jack a kiss from me.
对不起我没有信守承诺带个新的回去
I'm sorry I didn't get the replacement like I promised.
我知道他多喜欢那个
I know how dear it was to him.
我努力了
And I did try.
我们都努力了
We all tried.
我希望你能照顾好他
I hope you can look after him.
以及格雷姆  我爱你
And, Graham, I love you.
你们所有人
And all of you.
我永远爱你们
I've always loved you all.